Someone else who's taking control Taylor Swift
有人正在控制泰勒·斯威夫特
She has dropped the first song from her sessions where she is re-recording
她放弃了她的第一首歌的伴奏
all the song from her first six albums in order to gain back control of her masters
正在重新录制她前六张专辑里所有的歌以便获得主导权
Yeah she has decided to start with her second album fearless
是的她正准备她的第二张专辑《无畏》
so the original album cover is on the left that album was released in 2008
所以原始的专辑是左边在2008年发行的
and went on to win album of the year at the grammys on the right
右边是格莱美年度最佳专辑奖
is the album cover for Taylor's re-recorded version
这张专辑的封面是泰勒重新录制的版本
she'll release the full album on April 9th
她将发行所有的专辑在4月9日
but overnight she dropped Taylor's uh
但是一夜之间她放弃了泰勒的
she dropped a version of that album's original first single love story
她放弃了那个专辑版本的首支原创单曲《爱情故事》
Yeah here's what Taylor told Apple music's zayn low about the process of
是的这就是泰勒告诉苹果音乐的泽恩·洛关于
revisiting and then reimagining all these old songs
重新回顾这些老歌的过程
It makes me feel really close to those songs again
这使我再一次离这些歌更近了
and it also reminds me that obviously I want to keep a lot of
并且这也让我想起我当然想要保持很多劲爆的惊喜
cool surprises for the fans until I'm ready to show them fully to everyone
给我的粉丝们，在我完全准备好之前我都会保密
but the reason that I feel so passionately that artists should own their catalogs
但我之所以如此坚定地认为艺人应该拥有他们作品的版权
is because if you are the creator of all of this music
是因为如果你是这些音乐的创作者
you're the only one who actually knows the ins and the outs of it
唯有你，才知道这些作品的来龙去脉
you’re the only one who knows what almost was written
唯有你，才知道作品未采用的部分是什么
you're the only one who knows the kind of
唯有你，才知道创作历程的心路经历
secrets of the journey of making this music so you're actually the only one
所以你是那个唯一有能力的
who has the ability to share it with the fans in the way that
知道用什么方式和歌迷分享作品的人
that can make everyone the happiest and the most excited
能让所有人幸福激动不已的
so it's been really fulfilling in a way that I
所以在某种程度上我已经很满足了
I had no idea what to expect you don't want to feel like
远远超过了我的期待，你不希望重温旧作时
it's like you know your homework got destroyed
会像是作业做的太差了
and so now you have to redo your homework
然后现在再重做一次
it's not like that at all
我完全没有这种感觉
Yeah
是啊
it's yeah it's not like that at all
完全不是这样的
it's extremely fulfilling
真的很满足的
Robby says 2021 where women are taking control of their lives
罗比说2021女性将会掌控自己的生活
I'm living for this
我觉得有道理
coach says I'm excited for this now debbie says love Taylor
蔻驰说我很激动黛比说喜欢泰勒
did you guys listen to the new version thoughts
你们听过新版本吗，有什么想法呢
Yes Are you kidding me
当然，你在开玩笑吗
I was losing my mind
我都要失去理智了
Oh my god it's perfect
哦天哪，这太完美了
it's like it's so perfect because it's the same enough
就好像如此完美因为足够相似
that I'm not like Oh you've changed it
我不是那种，哦你改变它了
it's a classic don't change it
这是经典，别改变它
but it's new enough that her voice the clarity in her voice
但是她的声音听起来不一样了，更清晰了
the way that she sings the tonality just like the calmness
她唱的音调很平静
I mean she's an adult now so her voice is sounds different
我是说她成年了所以她的声音听起来不一样了
it is so cool to make music when you're a teenager
当你处于青年时期时，做音乐是非常酷的
and obviously I have records that I listen to and I'm like oh my god
很显然我听我之前的录音带我是:哦我的天哪
my voice when I was 14 or 16 or 18
我14，16或者是18的声音
you know to go back as an adult woman and re-sing them
你知道在成年时回顾并且重新演唱他们
and fix the little things that have probably been driving her crazy for 13 years
解决了那些让她抓狂了13年的小问题
is incredible but it sounded I am so excited and then the new cover like
这太不可思议了，我听时非常兴奋
I was so here for this this is so good I can't I'm like I Iove it I love it
新的版本太好了，我情不自禁地爱上了
you know we interview a lot of artists who have been singing a lot of
你知道我们采访了许多许多已经唱一样的歌曲
the same songs for many many years for decades even sometimes
很多年甚至长达几十年的艺术家
and one of the things we talk about is like
我们讨论的其中之一的事情就是
what's your relationship to a song now
你和这个歌的关系如何了
like you've been singing a song for 20 years
就像你已经唱这首歌20年了
you're not the same person that you were
但你已经不是之前的你了
when you first wrote it or when you first performed on stage
不是当初你写歌时或是初次登台表演的你了
you've grown you've learned so many things
你已经长大了并且学会了更多
so how does that affect the way that you sing this song
所以这将会怎样影响你的演唱方式
and you can hear that like you can hear that growth
并且你能听到你可以从中听到成长
you can hear that change that emotional maturity in the new recording
你可以在新的专辑中听到情绪成熟上的改变
and for Taylor Swift fans that have been on this journey with her
对于泰勒斯威夫特的粉丝来说就是和她来了一场旅行
from day one like this is a beautiful gift to them right
赠予他们一个非常美好的礼物
oh yeah Jeff says Taylor's a true legend fully standing in her power
哦是的，杰夫说泰勒是个真正传奇的人物
and demanding respect I'm so proud of her
我为她感到骄傲
Okey I don't want this to be taken the wrong way okay
好吧，我不想让你误会，好吗
so I listen to the new version no I'm not knocking it but I'm just saying
所以我听了新版本，我不是在否定，我只是说
I didn't hear any difference whatsoever
我没有听到什么不同
I'm not saying that in a bad way like I listened to the new version
我不是说它不好，就像我听了新版本
and then I went and put back the old version I'm like
之后我又把我喜欢的旧版本放回去了
what's the difference here no like so what are the differences
这里有什么区别？ 不，没什么， 所以区别在哪里
honestly is it lyrically different isn't it
实话说他在抒情上是不同的，不是吗
okay first of all audio
好的，首先是音频
instrumentation it's it sounded like
乐器听起来像
audio quality 13 years ago today
13年前的音频质量与今天相比
tell me about production okay production wise
告诉我关于制作，制作更加巧妙
the microphone I mean there's not much change
麦克风，我是说这个没有太大变化
it's very different but her voice
变化的是她的声音
no no no it's important knows the quality of the microphone
不不不，要知道麦克风的质量是很重要的
13 years ago till now
13年前到今天
it's going to capture certain nuances in the voice
它将捕捉声音中某些细微的差别
that you're not going to have 13 years ago
这在13年前不会有的
just the fact that her voice has evolved so much since then
只是她的声音从那以后有了很大的发展
as a music lover and maybe I'm just a specific obviously
作为一个音乐爱好者，也许我只是特定的
I say I know sounds when I listen to it
我说我听到的时候知道
you can hear listen to them side by side you can hear a child versus an adult
你可以将她的声音放在一起，你会听到孩童与成人的声音
singing the song you can hear it in her voice
演唱这首歌，你可以从她的声音中知道
It's a completely different quality of her voice
她的声音质量完全不同
it's just like it's profound you hear the growth
这就像你听到的成长
it might sound exactly the same in that it's classic
听起来可能完全一样因为它足够经典
but y'all tripping what it is different
但是你们都知道这有什么不同
play that in ant system right now
现在就是处于蚂蚁系统中演奏
it's gonna hit the way different
会有不同的结果
I think I understand a bit of maybe what you're getting at you graham
我想我能理解你的意思，格雷厄姆
like we know that this is primarily first it's a business decision right
就像我们知道这第一次主要是一个商业决策是吗
like first this is a business decision
首先，这是一个商业决定
because this is about her taking control of her business
因为这是关于她掌控自己的生意
and it's something that she wants to do
这是她想做的事
and it's something that she should be doing
这也是她应该做的事
but the art of it that comes out of it
但是从中产生的艺术
I think for her fans is something that they are going to really appreciate
我认为对于她的歌迷来说，这是他们非常欣赏的
right yeah like I'm not knocking okay keisha
是的，就像我不是在否定，好吧凯莎
I have a question for you
我有个问题想问
because we kind of talked about this before
因为我们以前讨论过这个
like is she going to change songs at all like so are would you be fine
就像她会完全换掉这些歌吗？这样你会没事吗？
if she records these six albums all those songs pretty much sound
如果她录制这六个专辑中所有的歌都非常完美
like love story dead in terms of like they pretty much sound exactly the same
就像《爱情故事》他们听起来几乎一模一样
she's just updating the quality of the sound and the microphone
她只是在更新声音和麦克风的质量
are you gonna be okay if there's really no changes at all
如果真的没变化，你会没事吗？
re-recording the master for me
重新录制主音乐
when the records that are as classic as they are
当那些像他们一样经典的唱片
most people don't like when a classic is changed at all
很多人不喜欢经典的改变
I think she's already showcased that she was able to re-recreate
我认为她已经充分展示了她能够重新创作
a classic that is not going to tweak my ear when I'm driving along
当我开车时我的耳朵不会受到伤害
when the radio decides to swap the old version for the new version
当收音机将旧版本换为新版本的时候
it's not going to be enough of a
这还不够
what is this this doesn't even have the same nostalgia
这是什么？这甚至没有同样的怀旧
it has the same nostalgia but the quality is better
这是同样的怀旧只是质量更好了
it's almost like taking something in like pink floyd era
就像是接受了平克·弗洛伊德时代的东西
and remastering it now
现在就重新创作
but the quality is just different
但质量就会不同
that's why all those remastered projects
这就是为什么所有那些重建的项目
from the back in the day are just so incredible
从后面的那一天开始就不可思议了
I'm okay with that
我是没意见的
if she wants to deviate give me a live version
如果她想要给我新的版本
give me the acoustic give me the remix album give me all the other versions
给我音效给我混音专辑给我其他所有的版本
if you want to go repurpose things
如果你想改变事情的目的
but you know what she's so nifty
但是你是知道她这么漂亮
that's the word I'm gonna Taylor Swifty is very nifty
我要说的这个词是泰勒斯威夫特是这么漂亮
she's gonna find a way to make everybody satisfied okay
她正在找到一种方式让所有人都满意的好吗？
right that's what I know about I'll just leave it at that okay
对，这就是我所知道的，就这样算了好吗？
let it go
随他去吧
okay no I'm not upset
好吧，不，我没有不高兴